Finding Aid for the Photograph Album Collection LSC.0094
UCLA Library Special Collections
Photograph Album collection
circa 1860
UCLA Library Special Collections
LSC.0094
1 unknown (301 oversize boxes)
This collection, like Picture Collection 99, contains photographs etc. of both persons and places and is intended as a supplement to other collections in the Department. It contains both bound and boxed sets of photographs which are too bulky to be located with Picture Collection 99.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9942335823606533
Scope and Content
Collection consists of thousands of photographs, some with descriptions and titled albums. California, Latin America, and the Middle East are well represented. Other subjects include railroad locomotives, photographs of British soldiers in the 1860s, South Africa, French actress Constant Coquelin, Australia, Egypt, Italy, Queen Victoria's 1897 Diamond Jubilee, the Canadian Rockies, Texas oil fields, Mexican Revolution, Mathew Brady photographs of soldiers and civilians, Abraham Lincoln, China, France, photographs of architectural drawings, New Zealand, Fiji, Persia, Scotland, Burma, Athens, Philippines, St. Petersburg, Japan, Hawaii, Sakhalin snow crystals, Dutch East Indies, Hopi Indians, West Indies, Turkey, Vatican sculptures, World War I photographs from France and Belgium, U.S. Navy midshipmen in the 1860s, pictures of people involved in the French Commune of 1871, and photographs of London.
Photograph albums.
- California Development Company photographs. v.p. (California & Arizona)., 1903-1908; no.1; (2 boxes of Disbound albums with mounted photographs)
  Scope and Contents note
  Showing irrigation work of California Development Company along the Colorado River and in the Imperial Valley, and the effects of the water flowing through the Colorado River Crevasse into the Salton Sink.
- Mulholland Highway, city of Los Angeles, Board of Public Works, D.L. Reaburn, construction engineer. Book no.2., 1924; no.2; (2 boxes of photographs)
- Somalia. [Rome, A. Antinori]., [n.d.]; no.3; (2 vol.)
  Collection of mounted photographs of Somaliland at time of Italo-Ethiopian War, 1935-1936[?].
- Eritrea. [Rome, A. Antinori]., [n.d.]; no.4; (6 vol.)
  Collection of mounted photographs of Eretrea at time of Italo-Ethiopian War, 1935-1936[?].
- Illustrations for Pioneer days in Kern County by Arthur S. Crites., no.5; (1 vol., unpaged looseleaf notebook with 43 original photographs and 4 maps)
  Pioneer days in Kern County by Arthur S. Crites. Los Angeles: Ward Ritchie Press, 1951.
- The company's rolling stock and buildings., no.6; (4 boxes of photographs)
- Locomotives belonging to various railroads in the United States and Canada., circa 1890-1940; no.7; (62 photographs in one album)
  General note
  Purchase: 1951.
- Hollywoodland [and] Dana Point, California., no.8; (63 photographs)
  A collection of views of homes, buildings and proposed land development in these communities by S.H. Woodruff, Community Developer. Included are views of the French and Italian Rivieras, apparently as possible models for Dana Point.
- Historic Monterey., no.9; ([Photograph album] with 21 photographs)
- Views of ancient buildings. Leicestershire., 19th century; no.10; (1 vol. with steel engravings)
- Color photogravures, Yellowstone park., no.11; (20 color photographs)
  "Printed in Germany"
- Hand-colored [photographs]. [San Francisco and Los Angeles, Pacific Novelty Company]., no.12; (12 colored photographs)
- [Brooklyn, New York]., [c. 1902]; no.13; (24 photographs [photomechanical reproductions])
- [Scrapbook of photographs taken by Lummis in New Mexico and Southern California]., [circa 1880-1920]; no.14; (53 photographs [cyanotypes])
- Riverside [California]., no.15; (Photograph album with 13 photographs)
  Views of the Everest Ranch and ranch house, "Descanto," in the Arlington district of Riverside.
  [Negatives available]
- [Virginia Picture album] [Old Point Comfort, Virginia, J.B. Kimberly]., [n.d.]; no.16; (21 leaves)
- [San Fernando Valley?]., no.17; (47 photographs)
  Note on album cover: (San Fernando Valley?); tentatively identified as Paso Robles by a relative of Whitley, 1987.
- [Early photographs of San Diego, California and Coronado Beach]., [1880s]; no.18; (22 photographs)
- [British soldiers of the 1860s]. [London]., [1867?]; no.19; (62 leaves of photographs)
- A trip to the Pacific Northwest via Southern Pacific Railroad., no.20; (25 leaves of photographs)
- Southern California., no.21; (35 photographs)
  Among the identified photographs are Views of San Diego Bay, Hotel del Coronoado, DuBois residence in Riverside, Moqui squaws, San Juan Capistrano mission, San Luis Rey mission, San Luis Obispo, Indian wood carrier, San Diego mission, view from Villa Hotel in Redlands, Mojave Indians, and Santa Barbara mission.
- Calotype albums. England., 1850-1856; no.22; (2 vol., 33 × 27 cm.)
  vol.1) "Photographic Experiments, 1850-1851" by an unidentified photographer; castles and churches in the style of Fox-Talbot.
  vol.2) Album of Alfred Capel Cure with his bookplate, quite likely his own work. In addition to views of his home, Blake Hall, Essex, there are views of English and Irish buildings, portraits of Irish villagers and of Cure and his camera.
  Many of the calotypes are faded.
- Album [of portraits]., no.23; (29 photographs)
  Many portraits are identified.
  Ex-libris: Mrs. L.C. Winchester, Elgin, Illinois.
- Album [of portraits]., no.24; (73 photographs)
  Unidentified.
- Santa Fe route., no.25; (63 photographs)
  Photographs include various scenes in Southern California, Arizona and New Mexico.
  1. Arrowhead Hot Springs, California -- Views.
  2. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railroad -- Views.
  3. Canyon Diablo, Arizona -- Views.
  4. Flagstaff, Arizona -- Views.
  5. Fort Wingate, New Mexico -- Views.
  6. Gallup, New Mexico -- Views.
  7. Hesperia, California -- Views.
  8. Highland, California --Views.
  9. Indians of North America -- Southwest, New -- Views.
  10. Laguna, New Mexico -- Views.
  11. Los Angeles -- Views.
  12. Lowe, Montana -- Views.
  13. Ontario, California -- Views.
  14. Pasadena, California -- Views.
  15. Rancho Camulos, Ventura County, California -- Views.
  16. Rancho Santa Anita, Los Angeles, County, California -- Views.
  17. Redlands, California -- Views.
  18. Redondo Beach, California -- Views.
  19. Riverside, California -- Views.
  20. San Bernardino Mountains -- Views.
  21. San Diego, California -- Views.
  22. San Gabriel Mountains -- Views.
  23. San Jacinto, California -- Views.
  24. San Juan Capistrano, California -- Views.
  25. San Juan Capistrano mission, California -- Views.
  26. Santa Catalina Island, California -- Views.
  27. Santa Monica, California -- Views.
- [Photograph album of South Africa]., no.26; (30 photographs)
  Views are mostly of South Africa but also include St. Helena (Island) and Madeira.
- [Photograph album of moving picture actors] Compliments Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences to the visiting British journalists. Los Angeles., 1928; no.27; (37 photographs)
  Presentation copy given to Edward A. Dickson. Removed from the Edward A. Dickson papers.
  1. Bancroft, George, 1882- -- Portrait.
  2. Banky, Eilma, 1903- -- Portrait.
  3. Barrymore, John, 1882-1942 -- Portrait.
  4. Barthelmess, Richard, 1897- -- Portrait.
  5. Blue, Monte, 1890- -- Portrait.
  6. Bow, Clara, 1906- -- Portrait.
  7. Boyd, William, 1898- -- Portrait.
  8. Chaney, Lon -- Portrait.
  9. Chaplin, Charles, 1889- -- Portrait.
  10. Chevallier, Maurice, 1893- -- Portrait.
  11. Colman, Ronald, 1891- -- Portrait.
  12. Costello, Dolores, 1905- -- Portrait.
  13. Daniels, Bebe, 1901- -- Portrait.
  14. Davies, Marian, 1900- -- Portrait.
  15. Del Rio, Dolores, 1905- -- Portrait.
  16. Denny, Reginald, 1891- -- Portrait.
  17. Dix, Richard, 1894- -- Portrait.
  18. Dove, Billie, 1904- -- Portrait.
  19. Fairbanks, Douglas, 1883-1939 -- Portrait.
  20. Farrell, Charles, 1902- -- Portrait.
  21. Garbo, Greta, 1906- -- Portrait.
  22. Gaynor, Janet, 1907- -- Portrait.
  23. Gilbert, John -- Portrait.
  24. Griffith, Corinne, 1899- -- Portrait.
  25. Jannings, Emil, 1884-1950- -- Portrait.
  26. Lloyd, Harold, 1893- -- Portrait.
  27. Mix, Tom, 1880-1940- -- Portrait.
  28. Moore, Colleen, 1902- -- Portrait.
  29. Nagle, Conrad, 1897- -- Portrait.
  30. Novarro, Ramon, 1899- -- Portrait.
  31. Philbin, Mary, 1908- -- Portrait.
  32. Pickford, Mary, 1893- -- Portrait.
  33. Shearer, Norma, 1904- -- Portrait.
  34. Sills, Milton -- Portrait.
  35. Swanson, Gloria, 1899- -- Portrait.
  36. Talmadge, Norma, 1897- -- Portrait.
  37. Torrence, Ernest -- Portrait.
  Negative available of Gloria Swanson.
- San Francisco Views. San Francisco: Cardinell-Vincent Company, s.a., no.28; (23 leaves)
- Postal cards [of California]., [1905-10]; no.30; (150 photos)
  Most of the postcards are addressed to various persons in Los Angeles and Santa Ana. Views are chiefly of Southern California and San Francisco Bay Area cities.
- Views of manufacture and installations of product. Los Angeles., 1925[?]; no.31; (29 photographs)
  Marbelite Corporation was a manufacturer of street lighting equipment.
- Rocky Mountain Views on the Rio Grande, the 'scenic line of the world'., no.32; (22 mounted color plates of 24 quadri-colored engraved views from recent photographs)
  Made exclusively for the Van Noy News Company, Denver, Colorado; for sale only en route on the Denver & Rio Grande railroad (Denver: Smith-Brooks Printing Company, c.1913).
- [Photograph album of Constant Coquelin, the French actor, in various roles]., no.33; (27 photographs) (Box [94/24])
  Holograph inscription: "A Madame Larsonneux ... C. Coquelin."
- Australian views from Edwin Carton Booth's Australia. London: Virtue and Company, Limited., [1873-76]; no.34; (3 boxes with 88 mounted engravings, Colored by hand - Size of engraved surface is 7.5 × 4.75")
  Various Australian scenes.
  [Edwin Carton Booth's Australia is in SRLF (*DU 102 B64a)].
  Purchased in England in 1958 by Dr. Lawrence C. Powell.
- Monuments de l'Egypte ancienne et moderne. n.p., circa 1870; no.35; (1 vol.)
  Photographs of Egyptian antiquities and city scenes.
- European antiquities, architecture, art, and scenery., circa 1900; no.36; (4 vol. of photographs and reproductions)
  Contents:
  1. Rome.
  2. Florence, Naples, Assisi.
  3. Naples, Capri, Milan.
  4. Switzerland, Italy, Southern France.
  Identified photographs have been pasted into the albums.
- Glen Tilt. Dundee., 1871; no.37a; (2 vol. 32 × 39 cm. Photograph albums with approximately 65 [19 × 24 cm.] mounted photographs)
  Cover title. Depicts a country estate in Scotland with views of the house, the grounds, and various scenes of a deer hunt.
- Souvenir of Lude. Dundee., 1871; no.37b; (1 vol., 32 × 39 cm. Photograph album with approximately 30 [19 × 24 cm.] mounted photographs)
- Views of Scotland., [1880s?]; no.37c; (1 vol., 32 × 43 cm. Photograph album with various size albumen prints)
  Scenery and historical interiors, most of the photographs initialed in the plate, J.V., the binding gold-stamped J. Valentine Photographer, Dundee.
- European royalty, nobility, and famous persons., circa 1895-1910; no.38; (3 vol.)
  The photographs and clippings, which have been pasted into albums, are identified.
- London, Jersey, Guernsey, Sark, Staffa, Cornwall, Killarney, and other places., circa 1895-1905; no.39; (1 vol. of photographs)
- Niagara Falls, Lake George, Birmingham Falls, and other scenes of New England., circa 1880; no.40; (1 vol. of photographs)
- [The Alhambra and other European scenes]. [London?]., circa 1880; no.41; (1 vol.)
  Loose photographs of Italian works of art, and British military activities in Ethiopia have been removed.
- Views of Italy, England, and France [and U.S.A.] n.p., circa 1895; no.42; (1 vol.)
  Includes photographs of Roman art and architecture, the French Riviera (including some carnival scenes), and various English views.
- Souvenir de Firenze., circa 1890; no.43; (1 vol., mounted and illustrated)
  4 photographs of Pisa are included at the back.
- Views of Italian buildings. Venice., circa 1859; no.44; (1 album [43 × 30 cm.] with 24 mounted photographs, approximately 25.5 × 40 cm.)
  21 by Carlo Ponit. Possibly a variant of one of the series, Ricordo di Venezia, published by Ponti.
- The diamond jubilee naval review, at Spithead, June 26th, 1897. London: Marion & Company., no.45; (1 vol. with 16 permanent photographs, mounted and illustrated)
  A list in the back pocket identifies these mezzotints.
- Diamond jubilee procession, 1897. London: Marion and Company., no.46; (1 vol., mounted and illustrated)
  Procession in honor of Queen Victoria's sixty years' reign.
- Ricordo di Venezi., circa 1875; no.47; (1 vol., colored, mounted and illustrated)
- Queen Alexandra's christmas book; photographs from my camera. London: Daily Telegraph., 1908; no.48; (1 vol., illustrated)
- [Views of China, Japan, and Canada]. n.p., circa 1890; no.49; (1 vol. mounted and illustrated)
  Includes photographs of Hong Kong, Canton (showing an execution), various Japanese cities, and scenery of British Columbia, Canada.
- [Southern California views]., circa 1903; no.50; (1 vol., illustrated)
  A photograph album with scenes of New York and Ohio in 1903, an overland railroad trip to Southern California and Los Angeles, and scenes of travels in Southern California.
- Torrey Canyon Oil Company properties. n.p., 1910; no.51; (1 vol., of photographs, mounted and illustrated)
  Gift of Luis E. Kemnitzer.
- [Ventura county, Sulphur Mountain field oil explorations]., circa 1910; no.52; (1 vol. of photographs, illustrated)
- Film album no.1. n.p., Josetti., circa 1938; no.53; (36pp., illustrated [ports])
  Photographs of moving picture actors and actresses which came as premiums with cigarette packages.
- Washington in photogravure. New York: Harwell-Evans Company., circa 1900; no.54; (1 vol., illustrated)
  Gift of Mr. and Mrs. Ben L. Nicholas.
- The Canadian Pacific Rockies; a series of twenty-four hand colored photogravures. Banff, Canada: Byron Harmon., circa 1930; no.55; (1 vol., color illustrated)
- Texas oil fields and drilling. Wichita Falls, Texas., c. 1919; no.56; (1 vol., with 25 photographs, illustrated)
- [Los Angeles in photographs: one hundred views]., circa 1880-1920; no.57; (1 vol.)
  Negative is available of first photograph.
- South African souvenir. Durban: D'Urban & Kimberley., 1898; no.58; (1 vol., illustrated)
- Views of Chicago, Colorado, Salt Lake City, and California., circa 1910; no.59; (1 vol., illustrated)
  California scenes include: San Francisco after the earthquake, Long Beach, Catalina, Pasadena, mining camps, and Yosemite Valley.
- Postcard views of the Mexican Revolution along the U.S. border., circa 1911-1915; no.60; (Photograph album with 74 images)
  Portraits of military men of the Mexican Revolution; common graves and corpses of revolution casualties, military contest; a section of nature's wonders of new Mexico; and some portraits of C.C. Early in China.
- [Norway in pictures]., circa 1892; no.61; (1 vol.)
- La puce. France[?]., circa 1880; no.62; (1 album, 20 photographs, 14.5 cm.)
  A series of photographs depicting a young lady in various stages of disrobing as she searches for a flea.
  Ex-libris: Frederic Thomas Blanchard.
- Family album., circa 1890; no.63; (Photograph album with 100 images)
  Photographs of Columbia, Missouri, Texas scenes, and various rural and urban views of Mexico.
  Trip photographs from a small city in Texas to Mexico, including portraits of children, women, Blacks, horse-drawn carriages, houses, churches, street scenes, and panoramic views of Mexican towns.
- [Elysian Park railroad bridge construction in photographs]., circa 1910; no.64; (1 vol.)
  Gift of Robert E. Fessenden.
- Engineering photographs., 1911-[1917]; no.65; (1 vol.)
- [Family photographs and Southern California scenes]., 1898-1901; no.66; (1 vol.)
- [Portraits of prominent Englishmen and women, including royalty, authors, etc.]., circa 1875; no.67; (1 vol.)
  A few photographs of prominent Italians, e.g. Garibaldi, are included.
- California missions, Monterey, and Southern California. Glendale, California., circa 1936; no.68; (3 vol. illustrated with photographs [snapshots])
  vol.1) California missions.
  vol.2) Monterey, California.
  vol.3) Southern California.
- Cold Brook Camp., June 28-August 29, 1909; no.69; (1 vol.)
  Photographs of family camping and hiking. "Azusa, the canon city ... Los Angeles County, California," and undated booklet is pasted inside the front cover.
- Actors and actresses in stage costumes. n.p., circa 1890; no.70; (3 vol. ports)
  These standing up albums have unusual covers. One album also has a music box.
- Carte-de-visite photograph albums. v.p., v.d.; no.71; (2 boxes, nine items)
  - Soldiers and civilians, published by E. & H.T. Anthony., no.(1a, b); (72 portraits)
    Album is one of group published by Albert Boni.
  - [Photograph album]., no.(1c); (43 portraits)
    Album and cartes imprinted D. Appleton.
  - Men, women, children, a few of identified notables., no.(1d); (27 portraits)
  - The cast of The Two Orphans by Napoleon Sarony. Issued as a souvenir with title of play and name of theatre on binding., no.(1e); (21 portraits)
  - Union Army field grade officers, including Grant, Rosecrans, Sherman, et al. Most published by E. & H.T. Anthony., no.(2abcd); (189 portraits in 4 albums)
- Abraham Lincoln from the Frederick Hill Meserve Collection. New York., 1942; no.72; (1 album of photographs with 132 ports, 28 cm.)
  Prepared by Meserve for Ralph A. Gregory of Saint Louis, Missouri. Included are lists identifying the photographs and letters from Meserve to Gregory.
  Descriptions of 118 of these portraits will be found in Meserve's The photographic portraits of Abraham Lincoln (TR 16.5 L6M5).
  Gift of Albert Boni.
  Shelved in 94/71, Box 3.
- Shanghai and central China photograph album. v.p., circa 1920; no.73; (1 vol., 23 × 30 cm.)
  Photographs taken on a tour of China showing unidentified people and places.
- Doorways, windows, and spires of France. v.p., (France)., v.d.; no.74/1-2; (2 vols. 54 × 45 cm. Photograph album with photographs mounted on canvas)
  Showing examples of architectural detail on French buildings, chiefly doors, windows, and spires, some very elaborately decorated and of an early date.
  Ex-libris: Charles Boyer.
- Domestic architecture of France. v.p., (France)., v.d.; no.75; (1 vol., 54 × 45 cm. Photograph album with photographs mounted on canvas)
  Showing examples of the exteriors of private dwellings in various French cities.
- Columns. v.p., v.d.; no.76; (1 vol., 54 × 45 cm. Photograph album with photographs mounted on canvas)
  Showing examples of columns used on the facades of various kinds of buildings, chiefly ancient Greek temples, and showing details of columnar capitals.
- Architectural drawings. v.p., (France)., v.d.; no.77; (1 vol., 54 × 45 cm. Photograph album with photographs mounted on canvas)
  Showing various French buildings and monuments and also their floor plans.
- French half-timber work. v.p., (France)., v.d.; no.78; (1 vol., 54 × 45 cm. Photograph album with photographs mounted on canvas)
  Showing examples of half-timber work on French buildings, some dating from the 15th century.
- French monuments. v.p., (France)., v.d.; no.79; (1 vol., 54 × 45 cm. Photograph album with photographs mounted on canvas)
  Showing French historical, literary and military monuments and statuary.
- French châteaux. v.p., (France)., v.d.; no.80; (2 vols. 54 × 45 cm. Photograph albums with photographs mounted on canvas)
  Showing French chateaux with some views of architectural detailing, courtyards and interiors.
- Architectural metal work and arches in France. v.p., (France)., v.d.; no.81; (1 vol., 54 × 45 cm. Photograph album with photographs mounted on canvas)
  Showing ironwork doors, wrought iron gates, grilles and other metal work. The album also includes views of arches and archways, some monumental.
- French churches. v.p., (France)., v.d.; no.82; (3 vols. 54 × 45 cm. Photograph albums with photographs mounted on canvas)
  Showing French church interiors and exteriors. Woodcarving work, interior furnishings and church courtyard views are also included.
- Stratford works. Stratford, England., 1897; no.83; (1 vol., 35.5 × 22 cm. Photograph album decorated with small watercolors)
  Inscribed on front cover, To Sir William Birt, January, 1897. Photographs show rolling stock and the shops engaged in its production at Stratford Works. Included are many pages of signatures.
- San Francisco earthquake and fire. San Francisco., 1906; no.84; (1 vol., 18 × 28 cm. Photograph album)
  A collection of amateur snapshots showing the military, the streets and the people in the aftermath of the 1906 earthquake.
  Ex-libris: E.A. Dickson.
- Victorian album. Aberdeen., 1881-1892; no.85; (1 item. 22 × 20 cm. Padded tan suede photograph album with brass corners and hasp)
  A gift album with group and individual photographs.
- Sidmouth family album. Devon, England., circa 1875-1900; no.86; (1 vol., 30 × 25 cm. Photograph album)
  Containing many carte-de-visite, portraits and some large group photographs probably taken at Oxford.
- Southern California Edison Company, Long Beach steam plant. Long Beach, California., 1924-1929; no.87; (4 items. 26 × 35 cm. Photograph albums with approximately 500 [8 × 10"] photographs)
  Showing the construction of Steam Plants no.1-3. The plants were designed by Stone & Webster, Incorporated, Boston. Bishop was official photographer for the company from 1920-1930.
- Yosemite., [circa 1914]; no.88; (1 item. 27 × 23 cm. Photograph album)
  Among the photographs is one of David Curry, founder of Camp Curry.
- European royalty and nobility portraits. v.p., circa 1880; no.89; (1 vol., 15 × 24 cm. Carte-de-visite album)
- European photograph album. v.p., circa 1890; no.90; (1 vol., 29 × 38 cm.)
  Views of cities and tourist attractions in the British Isles, France, Italy, Germany, Switzerland and the Low Countries.
- New Zealand. v.p., circa 1886; no.91; (1 vol., 23 × 34 cm. photograph album)
  Scenic views of the hot spring and volcanic regions of New Zealand in the Rotorua district including the famous pink and white terraces which were destroyed in the eruption of Mount Tarawera, June 10, 1886. There are also portraits of Maoris and views of Franz Joseph glacier.
- Fiji., circa 1920; no.92; (1 item, 25 × 20.5 cm. Photograph album with 83 Kodak photographic postcards)
  Mainly of Fiji.
- Journeys in Persia and Kurdistan. v.p., 1890; no.93; (1 item, 34 × 43 cm. Photograph album)
  Interleaved with descriptive text.
  Cover title: Journeys in Persia and Kurdistan, by Isabella Lucy Bishop, London, 1891, is illustrated with pictures derived from these photographs. The camera work may be the work of Mrs. Bishop herself.
  Ex-libris: Caro O. Minasian.
- Italia [v.p.]., [n.d.]; no.94; (10 items, 22 × 17 cm. Mounted photographs. In a portfolio, mounted size 59 × 35)
  Photographs include Villa Medici, Florence, Villa d'Este, Tivoli, Villa Borghese, Rome, and Villa Farnese, Rome.
- West Park tract photograph album [Los Angeles]., [circa 1909]; no.95a; (1 item, 14.5 × 20.5 cm. Photograph album with 83 photographs, mostly 12 × 16.5 cm.)
  Showing typical California bungalows of a real estate tract bounded by Normandie and Vermont Avenues, and Thirty-ninth Place, and Forty-second Street. The tract was owned by Vail & Crane. Cf. G4364 L875 1909. Vail & Crane, realtors. West Park tract [Los Angeles, ca. 1909] Map.